- id: ckw-l23-4317
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - アプローチ
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l23-4319
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ツー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l23-4335
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ロック
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l23-4353
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - バブル
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l23-4353
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ランド
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l23-4356
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - カフェ
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l23-4359
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - オール
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l23-4367
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - レーザー
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l23-4373
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - オリンピック
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l23-4394
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - エリア
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l23-4405
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ガイド
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l23-4424
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ガソリン
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l23-4432
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - リード
  hint: "verbal noun (する verb)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l23-4434
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - リアル
  hint: "noun (な-adj)"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []

- id: ckw-l23-4443
  prompt: ""
  answers:
    - ペース
  hint: "noun"
  stage: -1
  unlocks: '9999-12-31T23:59:59+00:00'
  befuddlers: []
